(Leonard:)I'm missing something.
(Leonard:)Did you say something to Penny
about Alex?
Yes, and a fat lot of good it did me.
All she did was get mad at you.
(Leonard:)Why would you do that?
(Sheldon:)I needed advice about a woman.
(Sheldon:)I would have asked you, but if the
last few years have proven anything...
(Sheldon:)...it's that you can't tell a uterus
from a unicycle.
(Leonard:)At least I know not to blab to a girl
about somebody flirting with her boyfriend.
(Sheldon:)Good to know.
A few more helpful hints like that...
(Sheldon:)...you may find yourself
on the Council of Ladies.
Hello?
I see. What time?
(Sheldon:)Very well, then.
(Sheldon:)Huh. That was the Human Resources
Department at the university.
(Sheldon:)Apparently my assistant, Alex,
has filed a complaint accusing me of...